indulgd.com 2017-11-18

# Privacy Policy – Indulgd

Please read this Privacy & Cookie Policy carefully before using or proceeding to access this website. Your use of this website indicates you have read and understood this Privacy & Cookie Policy and indicates your agreement to abide by the terms herein.

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
The policies below are applicable to Indulgd.com. Any questions or comments you may have regarding this privacy policy, contact Indulgd.com.

Indulgd.com respects each individual user’s right to privacy. Indulgd.com and its site does not collect personal identifying information unless such information is specifically and knowingly provided from users during contests, surveys, sweepstakes, giveaways, site registration, or use of public areas, such as a forum. Indulgd.com may use aggregate forms of this information — not individual data — for marketing and promotional purposes. Indulgd.com does not supply identifying information to other companies, or uses such information for its own purposes including but not limited to email newsletters, unless the user “opts-in” for such purposes by specifically allowing usage. (Identifying information must necessarily be used when notifying a user of requested information, such as notification of a winning entry in a contest or sweepstakes.) Indulgd.com is not responsible for any actions or policies of such companies.

Indulgd.com uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. However, Indulgd.com is not responsible for any breach of security. If a Indulgd.com user knowingly provides personal information, such as a name or email address, in a forum or other public service, that user should be aware that the information provided can be collected and used by third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Indulgd.com.

Non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of Indulgd.com’s Internet servers or through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small text files a web site places on your computer’s hard drive to recognize repeat users and facilitate the user’s use of the site. Also, cookies allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data for content improvement, targeted advertising, and marketing and promotional purposes. Users should be aware that Indulgd.com cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or other third parties. Most browsers allow a user to deny cookies; however, users should note that cookies may be required to provide certain website features.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**COOKIES:**

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.

**NOTICE REGARDING ONLINE BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING:**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

**DOUBLECLICK DART COOKIE:**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to this website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**ATTENTION KIDS:**  
No information should be submitted to Indulgd.com by children under 18 years of age without their parent’s or guardian’s consent. Indulgd.com does not monitor the age of its user audience.

Indulgd.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting notice of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
